

Ljupcho Sindeliev

Software Engineer



Summary of Experience

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Angular 4, ASP .NET MVC, Web API (REST), Web Services (SOAP), Front End and Back end development. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor degree in computer science focused in Internet and mobile technologies from Ss. Cyril and Methodius University, Faculty of Natural Sciences and Mathematics - Institute of Informatics.

Employment Timeline:

Companies	Years	Role
Beelivio - Skopje	2020 - Present	Full stack Developer (ASP .NET MVC)
F5 Tech - Skopje	2019 – 2020	Full stack Developer (Angular 4+, .Net Core 2.0)
OpenGI – Skopje	2016 - 2019	Front End / Web Developer (Angular 4+, ASP .NET MVC)
Re:Aktiv – Skopje	2015 - 2016	Web Developer (ASP .NET MVC)
Vista Group – Skopje	2014 - 2015	Web Developer (Web Forms)
Total Experience:	6.5 years	



Education

Years of study	2010 - 2014
University	University Ss. Cyril and Methodius Skopje, Macedonia
Major/Faculty	Faculty of Natural Science and Mathematics, Institute of Informatics
Degree	Engineer of Internet and Mobile Technologies



Competencies

Skills, knowledge	Description
Development (languages)	Type Script, Java Script, HTML5, C#
Frameworks / Libraries	Angular 4+, ASP .NET MVC, Web API, Web Services, ADO .NET, Web Forms , Entity Framework, Angular Material, Bootstrap, JQuery, CSS, Kendo
Working Methodologies	Scrum, Agile, Kanban, Waterfall
Data-interchange format	JSON, XML
DB	MS SQL Server
Software Architecture / Patterns / Techniques	Three layer architecture, Onion architecture, MVC, MVVM, Dependency Injection, Singleton pattern, Responsive design etc.
Integrated development environment	Microsoft Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, NetBeans, MS SQL Server Management Studio
Source control systems	TFS (Team Foundation Server), GIT, GIT Extensions
Continuous integration	TFS (Team Foundation Server) , GIT, GIT Extensions
Task/bug tracking tools	TFS (Team Foundation Server)
Certificates:	CISCO CCNA1, CCNA2
UI/UX design tools / Animation and Multimedia	Adobe Photoshop, Corel Draw, Power Director, Audacity, Google Sketchup
Communication with clients	Via skype, email, Slack, Microsoft Teams face to face etc.



Languages

Language	Level
Macedonian	Native language
English	Advanced
Serbian / Croatian	Professional working proficiency



Personal Characteristics

Integrity		
Excellent problem solving skills		
Self motivated, dynamic and disciplined		
Self managed, quick learner		
Team player		
Able to meet deadlines		
Attention to detail		
Personal Information's:		
Born	19/03/1992	
Driving license	B - Category	
Mobile phone:	(+389) 075 / 612 - 374	
E-Mail:	s.ljupcho@yahoo.com	



Experience

2020 - Present Beelivio, Skopje

Beelivio - AIMS (Product oriented) (Feb 2020 – Present)

Role: Full Stack Developer (ASP .NET MVC)

Responsibilities:

- Developing new features for the APAVE Group ERP system AIMS.
- **About the Web App**: ERP system for Apave Group.

Technology used: ASP .NET MVC, Kendo UI, MS SQL

Application architecture / pattern: Factory pattern

Team Size: 6 developers + 2 QA

2019 - 2020 F5 Tech, Skopje

F5 Tech - Halza (Product oriented) (Aug 2019 – Feb 2020)

Role: Full Stack Developer (Angular 4+, .Net Core 2.0)

Responsibilities:

- Developing the Halza Web App.
- **About the Web App**: The Halza web app lets you securely store, track & share your medical data with doctors, family, and friends. All access is private and controlled only by the subscriber. It is safely stored on the Microsoft cloud and available 24/7.

Technology used: Front-end: Angular 4+, Back-end: .Net Core 2.0

REST application architecture: Hypermedia as the Engine of Application State (HATEOAS)

Team Size: 6 developers + 2 QA

2016 - 2019 OpenGI, Skopje

OpenGI - UI (Product oriented) (Start / End date: Jan 2018 – August 2019)

Role: Web Developer (Angular 4+, Web API, Web Services)

Responsibilities:

- Developing the Transactor* system from scratch in Angular 4
- Dynamic configurable application for different type of purposes (different insurance needs).
- **Structure**: One project for creating / generating JSON Configuration, another for rendering the JSON.
- Web API calls are in the backend.
- o Transactor system is sort of aggregate system of all insurgence houses that are signed in, in the system. The system is offering list of quotes to the user form different insurance houses. Then the user can select the desired one and convert it to the policy. Also there is option to pay via the system or to pay in cache. The data capture process is also implemented with the appropriate schemes for the appropriate insuring company. The system have multiple roles depending on the level of access (B2C user, insurer company broker etc).

Team Size: 5 developers + 2 QA

Acorn - Document Management Portal (B2C) (Start / End date: Sep 2017 – Dec 2017)

Role: Web Developer (ASP .NET MVC, JQuery, Bootstrap, JavScript, JSON, XML, Web Services)

Software Architecture: Onion Architecture

Description: Business to Customer (B2C) Web Application for: Acorn Insurance

Document Upload/Download application, for Acorn Insurance. Goal of the application is for a curtain logged account to show list of all policies referenced to that account, and then by choosing the desired policy the user can upload the required type of documents (Claims related paperwork, Multiple policy forms, Singular policy form etc) for that policy.

After fulfilling the form with documents, the user will be notified which files are successfully / unsuccessfully uploaded, and a notification mail will be send with the outcome.

In the back-office (Transactor System), there is also a notification mail for the insurer employ with the required data and attachment of the files.

Document download refers to the available documents predefined by the TCAS (Transactor System) administrator for the current policy. The user can download the document or bundle of documents, and also send the desired document on his own email. Application is mobile and OS (Operating System) friendly: IOS

(Safari), Android (Google Chrome, In build browser), Windows (Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Microsoft Edge, Internet Explorer), Mac OS X (Safari)

*The users can login to the application using their registered account on Acorn Insurance main web application, or can create a new one if some requirements are fulfilled (to be in Transactor System, etc).

Team Size: 4 developers + 2 QA

^{*}Application is integrated with Transactor system.

^{*}The application is multi brand (3 different layouts) for 3 separate line of business of Acorn insurance (Acorn Insurance, Motorcade insurance, Ladies first insurance).

Principal B2C Documents Management portal - Download Extension (Start / End date: Nov 2017 – Dec 2017)

Role: Web Developer (ASP .NET MVC, JQuery, Bootstrap, JavScript, JSON, XML, Web Services)

Software Architecture: Onion Architecture

Description: Extension of the current Principal (B2C) Document management portal with new features.

*New feature: Document download

Download the predefined documents (from Transactor TCAS administrator) for the selected policy. There i option to view the document in browser, or to directly download it.

Application is mobile and OS (Operating System) friendly: IOS (Safari), Android (Google Chrome, In build browser), Windows (Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Microsoft Edge, Internet Explorer), Mac OS X (Safari).

Team Size: 4 developers + 2 QA

REGIS Military Mutual Kit (MMK) - Business to Customer (B2C) Web Application (Start / End date: Mar 2017 – Sep 2017)

Role: Web Developer (ASP .NET MVC, JQuery, Bootstrap, JavScript, JSON, XML, Web Services, Web API (Swagger), OAuth framework)

Software Architecture: Onion Architecture

Description: Business to Customer (B2C) Web Application for: REGIS Military Mutual Kit (www.themilitarymutual.com)

Web application that covers the data capture process of getting a quote and/or buying a policy for REGIS insurance. Key features:

- *Implementation of sign in with Facebook, Google, Transactor (TCAS) user (current stored REGIS users). *Data capture process
- *Converting a quote to policy and buying it.
- *Implementation of SagePay, for purchase a policy.
- *Personal details view (Personal info, My Quotes, My Policies).
- *Email notifications
- *Responsive design
- *Cross browser (Internet Explorer 9, Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Microsoft Edge, Safari).

 Application is mobile and OS (Operating System) friendly: IOS (Safari), Android (Google Chrome, In build browser), Windows (Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Microsoft Edge, Internet Explorer), Mac OS X (Safari).

Team Size: 4 developers + 2 QA

Principal B2C (Start / End date: Feb 2017 – Mar 2017)

Role: Web Developer (ASP .NET MVC, JQuery, Bootstrap, JavScript, JSON, XML, Web Services)

Software Architecture: Onion Architecture

Description: Business to Customer (B2C) Web Application for: Principal Insurance (www.principalinsurance.co.uk)

Document Upload portal application, for Principal Insurance.

Goal of the application is for a curtain logged account to show list of all policies referenced to that account, and then by choosing the desired policy the user can upload the required type of documents (Claims related paperwork, Multiple policy forms, Singular policy form etc) for that policy.

After fulfilling the form with documents, the user will be notified which files are successfully / unsuccessfully uploaded, and a notification mail will be send with the outcome.

In the back-office (Transactor System), there is also a notification mail for the insurer employ with the required data and attachment of the files.

Application is mobile and OS (Operating System) friendly: IOS (Safari), Android (Google Chrome, In build browser), Windows (Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Microsoft Edge, Internet Explorer), Mac OS X (Safari)

*The users can login to the application using their registered account on Principal Insurance main web application, or can create a new one if some requirements are fulfilled (to be in Transactor System, etc).

Team Size: 4 developers + 2 QA

Bollington - B2B (Start / End date: Dec 2016 - Feb 2017)

Role: Web Developer (ASP .NET MVC, JQuery, Bootstrap, JavScript, JSON, XML, Web Services)

Software Architecture: Onion Architecture

Description: Business to Business (B2B) Web Application for: Bollington Underwriting.

Application covers the main three Line of Business (LOB): Taxi LOB, Courier LOB, Goods in Transit LOB.

Users can do: Quote, Re-quote for new policy, or do Mid Term Adjustment (MTA) for existing policy.

Data table is provided with search by: User, policy number etc. Application is integrated with Transactor system.

Team Size: 4 developers + 2 QA

^{*}Application is integrated with Transactor system.

2015 – 2016 Re:Aktiv, Skopje

Core Registry Platform (Start / End date: 2015 – 2016)

Role: Web Developer (ASP .NET MVC, JQuery, Bootstrap, JavScript, JSON, XML, Web Services)

Software Architecture: Custom / In house.

Description: Maintaining old and implementing new features to the main project of the company

Multiple Projects:

- CRP (Core Registry Platform). Generic platform for working with registers.
- Configuration portal Project: ASP .NET MVC project for configuring CRP (Core Registry Platform).
- Administration portal :ASP .NET MVC project for the technical support team. Used as part of the ticketing system for CRP(Core Registry Platform).
- Plugins: Part of CRP architecture.

Team Size: 15 developers + 3 QA

2014 – 2015 Vista Group, Skopje

Multiple Projects (Start / End date: 2014 – 2015)

Role: Web Developer (Web Forms, LINQ)

Software Architecture: Three layer architecture

Description: Self driven individual project, Maintenance of the developed projects.

Projects:

- Call Center: LINQ / Web Forms application. Build as layered structure: Data Access Layer (DAL), Business Logic Layer (BLL).
- Application for managing terminals, (devices used in super markets, shops), sales outlets, providing call support for the terminals, making tickets for the service department. This application include: insert, update, delete, activating and deactivating all of the above typesetting elements. Also includes inserting data using Excel spreadsheet, generating various reports and invoices (Excel documents). Access to the various parts of the application is limited by access user groups.
- WPF application for JSP Skopje TVM machine: Software for buying tickets (checking ticket status) for the JSP Skopje busses using: cash, mobile payment, credit card payment.

Maintaining / Supporting projects:

- ENAPSYS payment system: System for paying administrative taxes via mobile phone (SMS)
- ADR: software for generating certificates for transporting danger materials (used by Ministry of Transport)
- TACHO: software for generating tachograph cards for professional drivers (used by Ministry of Transport)

Team Size: 2/3 developers, no QA

2014 Internship: 4WARD (3 months) – Skopje as Web Developer